<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Elie Hymowitz</title>
    <link>https://ehymowitz.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Elie Hymowitz</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://ehymowitz.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://ehymowitz.github.io/post/experience/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ehymowitz.github.io/post/experience/</guid>
      <description>Download Link  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://ehymowitz.github.io/post/experimental/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ehymowitz.github.io/post/experimental/</guid>
      <description>Editing   Places People   Experimental Photo Filtering   Based on projects CSSgram and CSSFilters. Click on a filter to apply it, add sliders to tune.
 Photos    1977  Aden  Brannan  Brooklyn  Clarendon  Earlybird  Gingham  Hudson  Inkwell  Kelvin  Lark  Lo-Fi  Maven  Mayfair  Moon  Nashville  Perpetua  Reyes  Rise  Slumber  Stinson  Toaster  Valencia  Walden  Willow  X-Pro II    Remove Filter  Reset Sliders    Contrast    Saturation    Brightness    Sepia    Grayscale    Invert    Hue-Rotate    Blur     // Click Listener document.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://ehymowitz.github.io/post/people/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ehymowitz.github.io/post/people/</guid>
      <description>Editing   Places People   People Brendan Jess Casey Patrick Chanda Casper Janette </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://ehymowitz.github.io/post/photo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ehymowitz.github.io/post/photo/</guid>
      <description>Editing   Places People   Places Belize Vancouver Somewhere Art Osheaga St. Viateur Store Dog Beach </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://ehymowitz.github.io/post/transcriptions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ehymowitz.github.io/post/transcriptions/</guid>
      <description>Transcriptions Solos  Autumn Leaves - Chet Baker, Trumpet Solo  (Playthrough Link) There Will Never Be Another You - Chet Baker, Trumpet Solo  (Playthrough Link) Blue Bossa - Dexter Gordon, Sax Solo  (Playthrough Link) All The Things You Are in C# - Charles Mingus Quintet, Bass Solo (Playthrough Link)  Partial Transcriptions  Lingus - Snarky Puppy, Michael League Part  Spain - Chick Corea &amp;amp; Return to Forever, Stanley Clarke Part  Funk The Fear - Esperanza Spalding, Verse + Prechorus + Chorus Bass  (Playthrough Link) Psycho Killer - Talkings Heads, Verse + Chorus + Bridge Bass   Other  We Don&#39;t Care - Kanye West  Lost Woods (Ocarina of Time) - Koji Kondo  Mii Channel Theme - Kazumi Totaka    All transcriptions made with MuseScore  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Things</title>
      <link>https://ehymowitz.github.io/post/things/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ehymowitz.github.io/post/things/</guid>
      <description>As mentioned in the caption of this website I make music and things! Most of the details of how I&#39;m building what I&#39;m working on can be found on my GitHub page, but here are some of the projects I work on that are cool to see.
  Interactive Graphics  I initially made this for use with the haplet, but I ported it over to javascript using P5.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>